<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Saskatoon Guitar Studio</title>
    <link>https://saskatoonguitarstudio.github.io/hugotest/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Saskatoon Guitar Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 14:50:44 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://saskatoonguitarstudio.github.io/hugotest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://saskatoonguitarstudio.github.io/hugotest/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 17:02:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saskatoonguitarstudio.github.io/hugotest/contact/</guid>
      <description>Saskatoon Guitar Studio
2200 block of Haultain Ave. (in Churchill Adelaide Park)
Saskatoon
306-343-9191
email: info@saskatoonguitar.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons</title>
      <link>https://saskatoonguitarstudio.github.io/hugotest/lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 16:59:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saskatoonguitarstudio.github.io/hugotest/lessons/</guid>
      <description>The Lessons The lessons are private sessions that last 30 minutes each, once a week at the same appointed time. For music instruction, experience has proven that private lessons are the most effective, because each individual is able to work at his/her own speed and the courses can be tailored to each individual. As well supplemental material can be supplied to students who need more work in a particular area. The regular instruction season coincides with the school year: September until June.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://saskatoonguitarstudio.github.io/hugotest/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 17:07:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saskatoonguitarstudio.github.io/hugotest/about/</guid>
      <description>The Saskatoon Guitar Studio The Saskatoon Guitar Studio is operated by Walter Hofmeister since 1987. In that time Mr. Hofmeister has been one of Saskatoon’s most sought-after guitar teachers. He has taught hundreds of students and has 30 years of experience teaching almost every musical style and has taught all ages from pre-school children to senior citizens.
Since graduating from the University of Saskatchewan with a Bachelor of Music degree in 1987, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>